Oh, my God.
Christ!
Shit.
Oh, God. Oh, my God.
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
Think, think, think.
Oh, my gosh.
Okay. Come on, come on, come on.
Come on.
My name is Walter Hartwell White.
I live at 308 Negra Arroyo Lane,
Albuquerque, New Mexico, 87104.
To all law-enforcement entities,
this is not an admission of guilt.
I am speaking to my family now.
Skyler.
You are the love of my life.
I hope you know that.
Walter Jr.
You're my big man.
There are...
There are going to be some things...
Things that you'll come to learn about me
in the next few days.
I just want you to know
that no matter how it may look
I only had you in my heart.
Goodbye.
Money before the panel
earlier this year.
Happy birthday.
Look at that.
That is veggie bacon.
Believe it or not. Zero cholesterol,
and you won't even taste the difference.
What time do you think you'll be home?
Same time.
I don't want him
dicking you around tonight.
You get paid till 5,
you work till 5. No later.
Hey.
- Hey, happy birthday.
- Well, thank you.
You're late again.
There was no hot water again.
I have an easy fix for that.
You wake up early, and then you get
to be the first person in the shower.
I have an idea.
How about buy a new hot-water heater?
How's that idea?
For the million-billionth time.
- Did you take your echinacea?
- Yeah.
I think it's getting better.
What the hell is this?
- Hey.
- It's veggie bacon.
We're watching our cholesterol, I guess.
Not me. I want real bacon.
Not this fake crap.
Too bad. Eat it.
- This smells like Band-Aids.
- Eat it.
- So how does it feel to be old?
- How does it feel to be a smart-ass?